Thank you for watching
Robi-zaka Morning
Robi Slope
Oni no Bomber Car Inn
For the members who worked hard and ran through the year 2023, the program set up a year-end party for each term.
A party with only the members of the same term to close out the year 2023!
Except for the 3rd term members' year-end party this time
The 3rd term members' big year-end party
It's a little bit more mature than I expected.
So many cameras!
How fun!
The only place prepared for the party was the party hall, where there was no staff.
I heard that everyone brought something to the party.
That's right.
Then let's eat it.
Let's eat it!
Let's start with the foodies. Lipic's cooking.
Yes, Tohoku related? Tohoku. Nothing to do with Tohoku.
What is it? Homemade dumplings.
It's a totally different kind of party!
So Kubo went to work.
I'm making monkey tarts.
You've brought a lot!
It's delicious!
Gluten-free tart!
I knew it... conscious people eat gluten-free tarts.
That's why I'm surprised.
Great. Six-star tarts are gluten-free, too.
Two? Yeah, the two of us.
We are. What's this?
Korean food.
This is the chicken.
I'm so glad we did it.
We are. Baked sweet potatoes.
You just got them for me.
Yes, I'm so happy.
What is this? It's called a conversation?
You know, people like to talk. They don't buy the conversational stuff.
Okay, well, I'll just go with the candy.
Oh, it's heavy. It's heavy.
Get the Ramune.
Oh, this is great. What the hell is this?
You're right. I did bring the drink revelation.
I was thinking I'd like a soda.
Great. Is it me?
I brought something really special.
It's a scary bucket.
Bring some basashi.
No problem.
I'm just into it lately.
I'm glad you're happy. I love a good basasi bake.
I love it.
You know what you're doing.
That's great.
I can cut it right off.
I'm going to go with acai mole.
Grown-up.
I love it.
Maybe two kinds.
Adult
Yamashita brought such an acai ball.
Actually, there's a conspiracy behind this year-end party.
The year-end party for the 3rd term students is about to start.
In the midst of all this, I want to play a surprise on everyone!
What is it?
It's a cup of tea with citric acid!
There's a drink!
There's a lot of stuff on the table.
I'm going to make a cup of Senburi tea and citric acid.
I'll give it to someone.
Yamashita, who couldn't participate in the last Shikatemin Grand Prix
I'm going to surprise him at the year-end party.
I wonder where he will make his move!
I have to eat soon!
And look at his head!
Here's the head!
What head?
Oh no!
Sugar flavored sweet potato
Daigaku imo...
Ume taught me this
It changed my concept of "Daidaimo".
The best taro in the world!
You love sweet potatoes, don't you?
After the presentation of everyone's own dishes
Seino
Hamburger steak
It's all in the hamburger patty!
It doesn't look like roasted plum powder!
Cheers to Bananaman!
Cheers!
Ume-san too!
I'm going to put the queen in my acai bowl!
At the end of Four Seasons Radio.
I wrapped it up.
What time did you do it in the morning?
Mr. Plum.
I finished at 5:00.
In the morning.
The dumplings we made early in the morning after an all-nighter are finally ready!
Thank you for waiting!
Cheers!
Baked dumplings
Looks delicious!
Thank you for waiting!
Kabo Tokusei Gyoza
Gyoza dumplings, please!
So grown up! Plum blossoms and all!
It's like the private life of a CA.
Just like the dumplings at the restaurant!
Hot and tasty!
Yum!
I want some dumplings.
It's true... the CA is here!
You don't have these?
It's true... there's a CA.
There's a CA.
I'm afraid of this.
It's not here.
It's not right.
It's really not right.
Hey, man!
What are you doing, mikai?
It's not right.
really funny
Let's all give it up!
Early morning Gyoza Low Kubo main store
Kubo's main store was a big success.
Why don't you play something?
A bite
Want to play?
You're so calm.
There's a big difference between you and Gokhov.
There's a difference.
There's a difference, right?
Let's play Gokufu.
So we look for one member among the 11 who is talking about a different topic.
We all had to play "Word Wolf" together. The theme was love, which we found on the Internet.
Then, the majority of the participants popped each other on the head, and only one wolf hugged each other from behind.
Please find out the member who is talking about hugging only one person from behind.
So, I know what love is.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you!
I love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love.
I love, I love, I love, I love, I love.
Oh, I see.
It's your age.
But some people are like that.
I know, I know.
Does it make you more or less excited?
It goes up.
I think it would go down.
If it suddenly goes down, I'll stay.
Oh-ho!
What's this?
I hate this so much.
Are you okay?
I can't stop thinking about it.
Situations?
My ideal situation.
What?
When I'm sad.
Yoshida, anytime.
Me too. Anytime.
Something really mundane.
No routine.
Sometimes it's better to be cute
I think it's better if you do it before going out with someone.
I'm sure that's...
I'm not going to say that at all.
There's someone I like.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't.
It's the first time I've been in a relationship.
The way he looks at you.
It's the first time I've seen a face or a gesture that makes me hot.
If you'd done it before...
I don't really like it.
It's hard to choose between the two.
When you're in a relationship.
It might become the norm.
You don't meet someone you like
I don't take it for granted
I like the director
Thank you.
That one looks like it's across the street.
Now it looks like they're across the street.
The principal?
A little more.
Don't crush his head.
I'm not the principal.
What are you talking about?
I'm about to make a mistake.
I think you're the director.
Congratulations!
And this time, time is up after he mysteriously said he's the headmaster.
Who was that one guy, Wolf, talking about hugging people from behind?
Se-no.
If I do it one more time, I'm gonna do it.
Yes, I'll definitely go with you.
I'll be there.
I'll definitely go with you.
Only one of you had a different subject... the Wolf.
What?
It's a favor.
That's what I'm talking about.
You're really good at these games, aren't you?
You mean like a kiss?
You know, when someone touches you like that.
Uh-oh.
Extension.
Side of the stream.
Like this.
Touching like this
I get hit sometimes.
Hugging from the back
That's right.
Hugs and back hugs.
That's why I'm surprised.
I'm coming.
I'm going.
That was a blessing, right?
You know what?
It's so mature.
It's like CA's...
I know what a CA looks like when he's overseas.
I know what you mean.
I totally get it.
After the Word Wolf competition, which ended with a mysterious upsurge in excitement...
We received a paper bag from the program.
We took a survey of the most XXX person in the 3rd term to the 11 3rd term students so that we can present the results at the year-end party.
The results of the survey are here, and I will be presenting them in each category.
First of all, we would like to announce the ranking of the most likely to become the richest person in the third term.
The second place is the same as the first place.
Third place goes to
First, Reika Iwamoto.
I know, I know.
She's the youngest among the 3rd term students, but she seems to be the one who can save the most money.
From the time of her audition, she had the aura of a rich person.
The sense of a winner who will never run out of money in her life.
Who's that?
You did it!
Second place in the tie, Shiori Kubo.
I'm not surprised.
She doesn't seem to spend a lot of money.
I wrote that.
Second, I don't see her as someone who spends a lot of money, so I think she can save.
It says I seem to be able to save money.
Third, he lives a steady life.
Oh, that's it.
Facts
No. 1, who.
We're all in this together.
I think we're all the same.
I'll go ahead and announce who's number one.
I don't spend money.
Mr. Takaguchi.
I don't know...
It says, "I'll ask for a favor.
What's the reason?
I have a personality that can manage my personal affairs tightly
I think I can manage my money well.
Also, I'm marrying a rich man.
What's this?
Because I seem to feel good.
Aura of flowers and birds is the image of rich people.
That makes me happy
She looks like she's going to get married.
I think I'm going to marry someone with money
I want to get married in Hawaii.
I'm so happy!
I'm going to chase after him.
I'll be following you!
Next, which of the 3rd term students is the most idol-like?
Second place
Gan Gan
Mizuki Yamashita
The good one.
Not at all.
I think the reincarnated idols were born to be idols too
Eh who who who
Not yet...
Who's this? But they have a great spirit of service to their fans.
A professional idol who knows how to present herself
I could have guessed who would win first place. I could have guessed that too.
That's all I can say. Who who who who?
Shhhh...
I wonder who it is.
Ta-da!
ITALY
Italy.
Oh, my God.
I don't even need to do this survey.
The only one with all the questions. All of them.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
Really, really, really...
Ten seconds.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
Let's read the why.
I know why.
You're supposed to read it to yourself.
I'll read it to you sometimes.
But I'll read it to myself.
Great, great, great, great, great.
Now, tell me how to say hokko.
Like at a concert, or during fan service, or when you're an idol.
Who who who who?
The perfect idol from the beginning.
I have my own image of what I want to be.
You have a clear idea of what you want to pursue as an idol.
She has a clear idea of what she wants to express as an idol.
Leah's idolism shines on stage
Everyone's eyes are drawn to her
If it's not my impulse
The way everyone has to see it
Idol lyrics are not included
Everyone has to see it
But it's great that they match
You know the last song on "My Impulse"?
I heard the last music is coming out.
What?
Yes, yes!
Where's the camera?
It's the place to do it at this stage.
If that's all...
The third-term students have seen me do it for years.
I shouldn't say that I'm losing.
Here's a high jan winner.
Lilia would love to see that.
We can do it together.
We'll do it together.
I'll do it with you.
I like it... that's why my impulse is to make a face.
for the right to perform with Lilia Ito.
A rock-paper-scissors tournament
Whoever wins gets to perform with Lilia Ito.
First, we played rock-paper-scissors-paper.
Wow!
That's amazing!
I'm so happy!
I've never been so happy!
The entertainment for the 3rd term students' year-end party
Please enjoy my impulse Lilia Ito featuring Kaede Sato!
Okay, here comes the sound!
This is the best!
I'm not thinking about it.
I didn't think of anything.
What's wrong?
Tentententententententententententententententententententententententententententent
Cute!
He's so cute!
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
Go, go, go, go
Go, go, go, go.
Oh!
This is not gonna end.
It's not gonna end.
Come on, come on, come on.
It's over.
Laughter.
That's what I'm talking about.
Hey.
That's great!
Next up, the ranking of the three students I'd like to have as a girlfriend.
And this is where she finally makes her move.
What do you say? Say you'd like her to be your girlfriend?
That'd be great.
I've got one.
Which one?
Aya.
Who's it gonna be?
We didn't really go through them one by one.
We did the survey yesterday.
What did the group line say?
I'm in the group line too much.
Senburi naturally went in front of Kubo.
Yamashita with a calm face.
Will he succeed in surprising us without our permission?
No.2 I want to have Mee as my lover
Tomomi Sakaguchi
Wow!
I'll let you know too!
This is definitely Ume!
First of all, I love her face.
This one?
Yes, I do.
And then there's the fact that she's always so girly and elegant.
She's clean around her, and her belongings are well organized.
She's the type of person I'd like to have as a girlfriend because I can see how careful she is in her personal life.
She's a little girlish and cute.
I want her to be pampered in my presence.
I want to have a date at Daikanzan on my day off.
Let's do it!
That's great.
Because she's simply cute.
No. 1.
Eeeee...
Bang bang!
Yuuki Yoda
No way!
I really wrote it.
I wrote it, too.
Not only is she cute, but I love that she's so slouchy.
I think she'll let me do what I want, and I think the distance between us is just right.
You seem to have a good sense of distance.
I want to spend time with you, even when you start doing things I wouldn't normally think of doing
I want to spend time with you
I want to be in a convenience store
I'm not naive, I'm not naive, I'm not naive, I'm not naive.
that's great!
peanut camp.
It says something about a wrap tote.
yeah.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Okay?
What?
You did it.
We're doing a surprise.
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
I'm scared... from this moment on.
No... no, I'm not going to say anything.
We all knew.
What are you talking about?
Suddenly.
It's coming out of nowhere.
I thought I'd wait until we were all done.
You can say it now.
It's okay.
It's so bitter.
That's what I meant.
But Komori's the only one who laughed.
That's right.
That's why I was serving tea.
The lady distributing tea.
Farewell, Koizumi-san. I wonder if she'll make it.
I do little surprises like that.
Wait a minute.
Yamashita, who succeeded brilliantly, is going for more surprise combos.
Koizumi-san, too.
I thought something was wrong.
He said you don't trust me.
You don't trust him.
You don't trust me.
This is really just plain water.
It's not.
Yes, it is.
Real water.
There's water over there!
After Yamashita's double surprise combo, the jovial Mr. Len added
There's water over here.
Rynock in turtle
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Don't spill it sober.
Oh, this.
It's water.
Can I ask you not to spill it?
It's too plain.
Following up on the surprise, Saton spills it, too.
The chain of events that I didn't expect to see completed the three-way combo of temperamental chaos.
He's wearing those tight-fitting sleeves again, isn't he?
I should have worn something more fitted.
I hadn't thought this far ahead.
Maybe I should wear full body tights now.
Seriously.
And finally, I'd like to announce the MVPs of the third term, 2023.
I'll start with number two.
Second place goes to...
Sorry.
All third-term students.
Oh!
Adult
I was an adult.
Everyone in the third trimester did really well this year!
We all came in first place, and we all did our best.
Everyone was MVP, both for their individual work and for the national tour that the third term students led.
The seniors graduated, and the third term students led the group in their own way, and they're all so cool.
That's it.
That's fine.
On the other hand, I'm really curious about No. 1.
The first place is...
Rurutaaaan!
Yeah, yeah.
I couldn't agree more.
I'll read it.
You always put the people around you before yourself.
He's a very reliable captain, and he greets people on behalf of others.
He is a very reliable captain.
The year I took over as captain
the first tour as a captain, etc.
I want to thank you for your hard work and wish you all the best in the future.
I want to say thank you and I wish you all the best.
You worked very hard on the first tour after you became the captain.
I felt like I was facing one or two sides of you.
Thank you so much, Captain!
Thank you.
You're so mature.
Thank you for making me happy.
Umezawa shows his emotion when he was called MVP
And then...
I'm about to cry.
I'll be back in a bit.
It's nice.
A little thick.
Thank you.
And the air.
The water's not sweet.
Thank you.
I don't want to drink it.
Mukai showed those tears.
There was one last thing he really wanted to do with everyone.
Chocolate Disco.
When we talked about the game we wanted to play, he wrote "Chocolate Disco.
But I...
can't explain disco.
Chocolate disco game and
To the music.
You guess how many people in the room you are in response to the theme.
Face forward one by one
A rhythm game in which the aim is to succeed in which all the players do not fall in the same line.
First of all, these five players try to succeed.
The theme is
Punctuality
Who is punctual?
I see.
If one of us wins, the other wins.
It's still good to know you're in good company.
All right, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
This is gonna work.
Here we go.
He's cute.
That's the order of the day.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, here.
Definitely not.
Ha-ha-ha.
Last one.
I'd like to go for number five.
I see what you're getting at.
Toward the fourth and final one.
That's the last one.
First five.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's a really good match.
It's a great game. It's a great game.
I noticed.
You're late, but you're on time.
No, you're not.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's funny.
It's great, isn't it?
It's really good.
Next, the six of us will take on the challenge.
Here goes the challenge!
It's more fun than I thought it would be!
It's a lot of fun.
You're a generous person.
Generous people
People who are generous
You know, people who say they'll buy you anything
Yes, there are.
I'll go!
Oh, wow!
Wow!
It's amazing!
What the hell kind of six was that? It's my first six.
What kind of timing is not good, not good!
And while Sato was getting the same kind of criticism, it was time to call it a night!
Thank you for another year!
He said you're good. He said you're 6th place.
I was a bit naive in my self-analysis.
That's right.
To be told by your peers that you're 6th place, that's saying a lot!
My best friends think I'm a cheapskate.
Under Live general sale starts on the 13th.
Next time, 2023 is not over yet!
The too free year-end party for the third term students, where tears and despair intersect, has begun!
How was the 3rd term year-end party? Did you have fun and laugh?
It was like that. We are usually like this.
We are usually very disciplined. Thank you very much for your support this year.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating, we will be very happy to see you in the third term.
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel.